Thinking this friends, your friend Yogendra Verma is a
Jeev Vich Sales Manager friends, you are
very welcome to subscribe to my channel
and happy new year I request all of you to
subscribe to the channel
and it is your
duty to subscribe to such people, such people give their
feedback, the other company is IS Somewhat
and there is a huge volume here,
friends, here you need three types of subscriptions,
now to subscribe to the school yoga
na dharna, if you have
not subscribed to the appointed channel then
click on subscribe, after that
subscribe after making the payment and those who do
not want to
subscribe,
now we have to look back that there is no
tablet of any kind here, you can do quantity
10:00 instead of 4G or
you have any target from a single moment, this is not
any commitment of any particular volume,
but friends, with hope, one
thing is that earlier there was never such opposition, this is the
first time that
you have so much opposition on the table, I will take only those people who
want to do the work of the Sangh, the
people working here will always
take you  This recipe is
very
powerful, just
subscribe to any other company just to pass the exam,
open the subscribe thing so that you
can earn, they can make their own policy, can
take payment by making elements, whether it is
looting the motor,
subscribe and
[music]
subscribe to me, I
hope you will like the yogi in some time,
please
contact us as soon as possible, send the product message,
you are absolutely carefree, you are making a mistake,
I hope there is no problem with your documents,
here the channel subscribe to the
recruitment process, you channel
subscribe to me,
turn on the torch light